Oh Bartleby nice jammies how dare you
Sonic the one and only stop not you
stupid machine oh hi big boy and will
even use the stone heads down by the
bitch for decoration in the law bed
Sonic what did you do oh nothing much me
and my pal Bartleby just fixed it so a
certain sister of mine can go you're not
half bad you want on the nose of society
you Sonic what you lighten up quite all
right I think our skeptical friend will
have his questions answered tonight Oh
Sonic you will be badass evening what
missing hey bottle but come on I'll give
you a lift oh oh good thanks Sonic meet
you back at the safe house by the way
please don't go so fast this time no
problemo hey my butt Bartleby Bartleby
my what Bartleby my buddy